shaboopie.com 2015-12-07

# Privacy Policy | shaboopie.com

### Privacy Policy

disclosed in this statement. This statement applies solely to information collected at  the Shaboopie.com website. This policy will be accessible from our home page, and will be updated when  necessary. Shaboopie.com is committed to protecting your privacy if you visit this website.

Shaboopie.com collects general broad information about those visiting this website. This helps us improve the site to meet visitors’ interests. This information is anonymous traffic data and is not personal information that could identify individual visitors.

Shaboopie.com offers links to other Web sites.  Please note that Shaboopie.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. You are encouraged to read the privacy policies of other websites, especially before you share any personal information with them.

Shaboopie.com does not use cookies to track any personal information about visitors. (“Cookies” are small text file that a website server places on a user’s computer hard drive to be a unique identifier.) Some advertisers or other partners may use cookies if they are visited. Companies that advertise on Shaboopie.com use cookies to track visitors who come via an Shaboopie.com link. A sales commission may be paid to Shaboopie.com, but Shaboopie.com is never informed of the customer’s identity.

Regarding Google and the [DoubleClick DART](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) cookie:

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

If you have questions or comments about the privacy policy of Shaboopie.com, please [contact us.](http://shaboopie.com/contact/ "Contact")
